Finding Aid for the Louis Thurston Nicholas Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Plays
  - Plays–Programs, Jan. 26, 1996–Nov. 14, 1997 (Box 285, Folder 11))
  - Plays–Programs, Jan. 22, 1998–Sept. 25, 1998 (Box 285, Folder 12))
  - Plays–Programs, Nov. 7, 1998–Nov. 20, 1999 (Box 285, Folder 13))
  - Programs–Television–Bell Telephone Hour, 1959-1960 (Box 286, Folder 1))
  - Programs–Recitals–Carnegie Hall, NYC, 1948–1976 (Box 286, Folder 2))
  - Programs–Casa de la Paz–“What is Man?” by Ron Nelson, (1973)–11-24 Julio 1966 (Box 286, Folder 3))
  - Programs–Festivals–Chicagoland Music Festival, 1954-1955 (Box 286, Folder 4))
  - Programs–Festivals–Congregation of the Arts–Dartmouth College, 1968 (Box 286, Folder 5))
  - Programs–First Pittsburgh International Contemporary Musical Festival-Nov. 24-30, 1952; “The Importance of Humor in the Arts” Town Hall, N.Y., Jan. 17, 1941 (Box 286, Folder 6))
  - Programs–Concerts–Florida Symphony Youth Orchestra; Grant Park Concerts, Chicago 1986; Music Critics Workshop, Louisville, KY, 1955 (Box 286, Folder 7))
  - Programs–Plays and Recitals–The Gilbert and Sullivan Festival Theatre, Monmouth, Maine, 1958 (Box 286, Folder 8))
  - Programs–Festivals–Grand Teton Music Festival, 1973–1975 (Box 286, Folder 9))
  - Programs–Student Recitals–Hardin-Simmons University, Texas (Box 286, Folder 10))
  - Programs–Kentucky High School State Music Festival 1957, 1959, L.N., Adjudicator; 16th Annual Jeannie Ball, Feb. 11, 1967 (Box 286, Folder 11))
  - Programs–The Thirteenth Festival of Chamber Music, Library of Congress, Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation–Oct. 30, 31, Nov. 1,1964 and Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge by Jay C. Rosenfeld (Box 286, Folder 12))
  - Programs–Concerts–Playbills for Majestic Theater in NYC (Box 286, Folder 13))
  - Programs–Festivals–Newport Music Festival, Rhode Island, 1972–1977 (Box 286, Folder 14))
  - Programs–Recitals–New York School of Music and Arts, 1926 (Box 286, Folder 15))
  - Programs–Oberlin College Conservatory of Music, 1988, 1989 (Box 286, Folder 16))
  - Programs–Recitals–Sigma Alpha Iota, 1940-1966 (Box 286, Folder 17))
  - Programs–Student Recitals–Southwest Baptist College (Box 286, Folder 18))
  - Programs–Recitals–Tanglewood Berkshire Festival(Boston Symphony Orchestra), 1957-1968 (Box 286, Folder 19))
  - Programs–Student Recitals and Festivals–Texas Schools and Universities (Box 286, Folder 20))
  - Program–“Long Enough We Now Have Lived in this New Land” University of Connecticut Symphony Orchestra and Choral Society” April 19, 1974 featuring “That Continent” by Walter R. Ihrke and newspaper review (Box 286, Folder 21))
  - Programs–Recitals–Southeast Missouri State College (Box 286, Folder 22))
  - Programs–Various local concerts–1997–American Russian Youth Orchestra; Henry Cowell’s Musical Worlds; William Hall Master Chorale Program (Box 287, Folder 1))
  - Programs–Local Concerts (Box 287, Folder 2))
  - Programs–Recitals–Nashville Area, 1909–1933 (Box 287, Folder 3))
  - Programs–Nashville Area; The Music and Arts Teachers’ Guild Inc., 1930-1956 (Box 287, Folder 4))
  - Programs–Recitals–Nashville Area, 1937–1990 (Box 287, Folder 5))
  - Programs–Concerts–Praising, March 10-13, 1975, Nashville, TN (Box 287, Folder 6))
  - Programs–Concerts in Tennessee, 1936–2002 (Box 287, Folder 7))
  - Programs–Recitals–Miscellaneous Tennessee Colleges (Box 287, Folder 8))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous Colleges (Box 287, Folder 9))
  - Programs–Music Conventions (Box 287, Folder 10))
  - Programs–Concerts, Recitals–Chattanooga, TN area (Box 287, Folder 11))
  - Programs–Concerts, Recitals–Knoxville, TN area (Box 287, Folder 12))
  - Programs–Concerts, Recitals–Memphis, TN area (Box 287, Folder 13))
  - Programs–Communicator–Easter Seal Telethon, March 7-8 (Box 287, Folder 14))
  - Programs–Eastern Music Festival 1974; The Taming of the Shrew; Music of the North; Carnegie Hall, 1951-1952 (Box 287, Folder 15))
  - Programs–Gabriel Faure’s Song Cycle La Bonne Chanson, Opus 61 and others (Box 287, Folder 16))
  - Program–Founder’s Program, Cadek Conservatory, May 23, 1965; Amaranth Club,1912– (Box 287, Folder 17))
  - Programs–Kentucky Derby Festival, 1985 (Box 287, Folder 18))
  - Programs–Newport Music Festival, Vol.4, 1972, Vol. 5, 1973 (Box 287, Folder 19))
  - Program–Bulletin Music Conference, Ridgecrest, North Carolina, July 1966 (Box 287, Folder 20))
  - Programs–Concerts (not local) including John Duke songs (Box 287, Folder 21))
  - Programs–American Women Composer’s Performance Concert, Oct. 17, 1975 (Box 287, Folder 22))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1934 (Box 288, Folder 1))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1935 (Box 288, Folder 2))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1937 (Box 288, Folder 3))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1939 (Box 288, Folder 4))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1940 (Box 288, Folder 5))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1941 (Box 288, Folder 6))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1944 (Box 288, Folder 7))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1958 (Box 288, Folder 8))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1960 (Box 288, Folder 9))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1964 (Box 288, Folder 10))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1965 (Box 288, Folder 11))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1966 (Box 289, Folder 1))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1968 (Box 289, Folder 2))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1969 (Box 289, Folder 3))
  - Programs–The Ann Arbor May Festival, University of Michigan, 1971, 1974 (Box 289, Folder 4))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan, 17th Season, 1944 (Box 289, Folder 5))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan, 18th Season, 1945 (Box 289, Folder 6))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan, 19th Season, 1946 (Box 289, Folder 7))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan, 20th Season, 1947 (Box 289, Folder 8))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan, 22nd Season, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 9))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan, 28th Season, 1955 (Box 289, Folder 10))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen,Michigan, 1965 (Box 289, Folder 11))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan, 42nd Season, 1969 (Box 289, Folder 12))
  - Programs–University of Michigan School of Music, 1932-1933 (Box 289, Folder 13))
  - Programs–University of Michigan School of Music, 1934-1935 (Box 289, Folder 14))
  - Programs–University of Michigan School of Music, 1936–1937 (Box 289, Folder 15))
  - Programs–University of Michigan School of Music, 1937–1938 (Box 289, Folder 16))
  - Programs–University of Michigan School of Music, 1938-1939 (Box 289, Folder 17))
  - Programs–National Music Camp, Interlochen, Michigan–Scherzo Yearbook, 1935-1936; 1938 Prelude (Box 289, Folder 18))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1976–1977 (Box 290, Folder 1))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1978 (Box 290, Folder 2))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1978–1979 (Box 290, Folder 3))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1981-1982 (Box 290, Folder 4))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1982–1983 (Box 290, Folder 5))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1983-1984 (Box 290, Folder 6))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1985 (Box 290, Folder 7))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan–1985 Calendar, Catalogue and Adjudication Manual (Box 290, Folder 8))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1985-1986 (Box 290, Folder 9))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan–1987–Adjudication and Regulations Manual (Box 290, Folder 10))
  - International Music Festivals Materials–Parchment, Michigan, 1987-1988 (Box 290, Folder 11))
  - Summer Master Schools–Chicago Musical College, 1939; American Conservatory of Music, Chicago, 1939; Chicago Conservatory (Box 290, Folder 12))
  - Programs–Eastman School of Music at the University of Rochester, Accumulated Repertory (1925–1954), Recordings, and Publications, 1955 (Box 291, Folder 1))
  - Programs–Eastman School of Music at the University of Rochester, Accumulated Repertory (1925-1955), Recordings, and Publications, 1956 (Box 291, Folder 2))
  - Programs–Eastman School of Music at the University of Rochester, Accumulated Repertory (1925-1957), Recordings and Publications, 1958 (Box 291, Folder 3))
  - Programs–Eastman School of Music at the University of Rochester, 1957-1973 (Box 291, Folder 4))
  - Programs–Indiana University School of Music, 1965-1966, Volume One (Box 291, Folder 5))
  - Programs–Indiana University School of Music, 1965-1966, Volume Two (Box 291, Folder 6))
  - Programs–Indiana University School of Music, 1966-1967, Volume One (Box 291, Folder 7))
  - Programs–Indiana University School of Music, 1966-1967, Volume Two (Box 291, Folder 8))
  - Programs–Indiana University School of Music, Musical Arts Center, 1972 (Box 291, Folder 9))
  - Program Book–North Texas State College, 1948-1949 (Box 292, Folder 1))
  - Program Book–North Texas State College, 1949-1950 (Box 292, Folder 2))
  - Program Book–North Texas State College, 1950-1951 (Box 292, Folder 3))
  - Program Book–North Texas State College, 1952-1953 (Box 292, Folder 4))
  - Program Book–North Texas State College, 1953-1954 (Box 292, Folder 5))
  - Program Book–North Texas State College, 1954-1955 (Box 293, Folder 1))
  - Program Book —North Texas State College, 1955-1956 (Box 293, Folder 2))
  - Program Book–North Texas State College, 1956–1957 (Box 293, Folder 3))
  - Programs–North Texas State College, 1942-1954 (Box 293, Folder 4))
  - Programs–The University of Alabama, 1949-1970 (Box 294, Folder 1))
  - Programs–Bay View Association, Bay View, Michigan, 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2))
  - Programs–Bethel College, North Newton, Kansas, 1947–1948 (Box 294, Folder 3))
  - Programs–The University of Colorado, 1945-1946 (Box 294, Folder 4))
  - Programs–The University of Colorado, 1946–1947 (Box 294, Folder 5))
  - Programs–The University of Colorado, 1947-1948; 1967-1969 (Box 294, Folder 6))
  - Programs–Juilliard School of Music, 1950–1951 (Box 294, Folder 7))
  - Programs–New Orleans Baptist Theological Seminary, School of Church Music, 1958, 1962–1963 (Box 294, Folder 8))
  - Programs–National Association for American Composers and Conductors, 1951-1952 (Box 294, Folder 9))
  - Programs and Exhibitions–Northeast Missouri State College, 1963–1964 (Box 294, Folder 10))
  - Programs and Exhibitions–Northeast Missouri State College, 1967-1968 (Box 294, Folder 11))
  - Programs–Music Centers and Concert Halls–Music Center: American Scandinavian Foundation (Box 295, Folder 1))
  - Programs–Music Centers and Concert Halls–American Theatre Wing, Inc.: Professional Training Programs, 1952 (Box 295, Folder 2))
  - Programs–Musical Dramas–Atlanta Municipal Theater: King Arthur, 1968 (Box 295, Folder 3))
  - Programs–Music Centers and Concert Halls–Symphony Hall: Atlanta Memorial Arts Center, 1968 (Box 295, Folder 4))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–Berea College Presents Paul Green’s “Wilderness Road”, 1955 (Box 295, Folder 5))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–Bolschoi Don Kosaken Konzert, 1989-1990 (Box 295, Folder 6))
  - Programs–Boys Choir/Orchestra–Boys Town Choir; Souvenir Program, 1968 (Box 295, Folder 7))
  - Programs–Music Centers and Concert Halls–The Patricia Corbett Pavilion, College Conservatory of Music, University of Cincinnati (Box 295, Folder 8))
  - Programs–Boys Choir/Orchestra–“America’s Singing Boys” —The Columbus Boychoir, 1954 (Box 295, Folder 9))
  - Programs–Musicals/ Dramas–Harold Prince presents Zero Mostel in Fiddler on the Roof, 1967 (Box 295, Folder 10))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–Lake Wales Amphitheatre: Florida Aflame, 1953 (Box 295, Folder 11))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–Kermit Hunter’s Horn in the West, 1953 (Box 295, Folder 12))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–Ronald A. Wilford Assoc. Inc and Jean de Rigault present Marcel Marceau, 1958 (Box 295, Folder 13))
  - Programs–Mannes College Orchestra, Michael Charry, Music Director–1991-1992; Converse College Piano Clinic, Jan. 1993 (Box 295, Folder 14))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–National Players: A Midsummer Night’s Dream, 1961-1962 (Box 295, Folder 15))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–St. George’s Episcopal Church (NYC) presents Benjamin Britten’s Noye’s Fludde, 1964 (Box 295, Folder 16))
  - Programs–Boys Choir/Orchestra–Ninos Cantores de Morelin–Singing Boys of Mexico, 1961 (Box 295, Folder 17))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–Oliver!, 1964 (Box 295, Folder 18))
  - Programs–Musicals/Dramas–The Stephen Foster Story by Paul Green, 1964 (Box 295, Folder 19))
  - Programs–Boys Choir/ Orchestra–Leopold Stokowski; All American Youth Orchestra, 1941 (Box 295, Folder 20))
  - Programs–Boys Choir/Orchestra–Tucson Arizona Boys Choir, 1960 (Box 295, Folder 21))
  - Programs (by State)–Alabama (Box 296, Folder 1))
  - Programs (by State)–California (Box 296, Folder 2))
  - Programs (by State)–Colorado (Box 296, Folder 3))
  - Programs (by State)–Florida–The Phil, Naples, Florida (Box 296, Folder 4))
  - Programs (by State)–Florida (Box 296, Folder 5))
  - Programs (by State)–Illinois/ Indiana (Box 296, Folder 6))
  - Programs (by State)–Kansas (Box 296, Folder 7))
  - Programs (by State)–Kentucky (Box 296, Folder 8))
  - Programs (by State)–Louisiana (Box 296, Folder 9))
  - Programs (by State)–Massachusetts (Box 296, Folder 10))
  - Programs (by State)–Michigan (Box 296, Folder 11))
  - Programs (by State)–Minnesota (Augsburg College) (Box 296, Folder 12))
  - Programs (by State)–Mississippi (Box 296, Folder 13))
  - Programs (by State)–Missouri (Box 296, Folder 14))
  - Programs (by State)–New York, (1909–1966) (Box 296, Folder 15))
  - Programs (by State) —New York–Houghton College (Box 296, Folder 16))
  - Programs (by State)–North Carolina (Box 296, Folder 17))
  - Programs (by State)–Ohio (Box 296, Folder 18))
  - Programs(by State)–Oklahoma (Box 296, Folder 19))
  - Programs (by State)–Virginia and Washington, D.C. (Box 296, Folder 20))
  - Programs(by State)–Wisconsin (Box 296, Folder 21))
  - Program–Middle Tennessee Council Boy Scouts of America, Scout Circus, April 1956 (Box 297, Folder 1))
  - Programs–Tennessee Education Association, Convention–Oct. 1951, Nashville; National Music Council, Meeting Agenda and Bulletin, 1950 (Box 297, Folder 2))
  - Programs–Nashville Arts Festival, May 12-19, 1957, 1959, 1962 (Box 297, Folder 3))
  - Program–Grand Ole Opry August 24, 2002; Opryland Promotional, 1978 (Box 297, Folder 4))
  - Programs–Recitals–Nashville Area Music Teacher Association, 1981-1986 (Box 297, Folder 5))
  - Programs–Souvenirs from a Life in the Arts from the Francis Robinson Collection, April 23–May 3, 1981 (Box 297, Folder 6))
  - Program–Shepherd’s Center of West End, 1991, 1992 (Box 297, Folder 7))
  - Program–Tying Nashville Together, June 24, 2001 (Box 297, Folder 8))
  - Programs–Local Concerts (Box 297, Folder 9))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1929-1937 (Box 297, Folder 10))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1950-1957 (Box 297, Folder 11))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1967–1994 (Box 297, Folder 12))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1950’s; 1960’s (Box 297, Folder 13))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous–Concerts, 1970’s, 1980’s (Box 297, Folder 14))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1911, 1920’s, 1930’s, 1940’s, undated (Box 298, Folder 1))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1940’s —1950’s (Box 298, Folder 2))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, Feb. 1, 1957–Feb. 12, 1958 (Box 298, Folder 3))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, May 1958-April 1959 (Box 298, Folder 4))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 298, Folder 5))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 298, Folder 6))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous–1962 (Nashville Arts Festival ) (Box 298, Folder 7))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1963–1964 (Box 298, Folder 8))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 298, Folder 9))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 298, Folder 10))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1969- 1971 (Box 298, Folder 11))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1971–1973 (Box 298, Folder 12))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 298, Folder 13))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous–Carroll Cloar, July 4-August 25, 1976 (Box 298, Folder 14))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1970’S (Box 298, Folder 15))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1980-1983 (Box 298, Folder 16))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, July 25, 1980–July 7, 1983 (Box 298, Folder 17))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 298, Folder 18))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 298, Folder 19))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous, Nov. 13, 1992--1995 (Box 298, Folder 20))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous (Box 298, Folder 21))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous (Box 298, Folder 22))
  - Programs–Miscellaneous (Box 298, Folder 23))
  - Notebook–Dates of Operas (Box 299, Folder 1))
  - Lists- Opera and other music in 19th c. Nashville (Box 299, Folder 2))
  - Lists of Opera performances (Box 299, Folder 3))
  - Lists of Operas seen (Box 299, Folder 4))
  - Lists of Operas seen (Box 299, Folder 5))
  - Lists of Operettas, Musicals, etc. seen by L.N. (Box 299, Folder 6))
  - Lists of Light Operas, Operettas, Musicals and where seen by L.N. (Box 299, Folder 7))
  - Lists–Operas seen in Europe, 1935, 1967, 1972, 1977, 1980, 1982, 1984, 1985, 1987, 1991, 1992, 1993, 1994, 1997 (Box 299, Folder 8))
  - Lists of Plays seen by L.N. to, March 1996 (Box 299, Folder 9))
  - Lists of Local Concerts Attended since Thanksgiving 1996–Thanksgiving 1999 by L.N. (Box 299, Folder 10))
  - Lists of Concerts Heard by L.N., (1992, 1996, 1997-98) (Box 299, Folder 11))
  - Lists of Violists and Cellists with dates heard by L.N. (some programs included) (Box 299, Folder 12))
  - Lists of Violinists with dates heard by L.N. (some programs included) (Box 299, Folder 13))
  - Lists of Instrumentalists with dates heard by L.N. (some programs included) (Box 299, Folder 14))
  - Lists of Novels, Short Stories, and Plays read by L.N. (Box 299, Folder 15))
  - Lists of Organ Recitals Heard by L.N. (Box 299, Folder 16))
  - Lists of Music Sold with prices (Box 299, Folder 17))
  - Lists of Plays seen on European Trips ( World, Early and Contemporary British, American) (Box 299, Folder 18))
  - Lists and Notes–Miscellaneous (Box 299, Folder 19))
  - Lists–Miscellaneous (Box 299, Folder 20))
  - Lists–Miscellaneous Notes (Box 299, Folder 11))
  - Lists–Miscellaneous Notes (Box 299, Folder 22))
  - Lists–Miscellaneous Notes and Papers (Box 299, Folder 23))
- Publications ( Collected by Louis Nicholas )
  - Piano Guild Notes, Sept.–December 1967 (Box 300, Folder 1))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1968 (Box 300, Folder 2))
  - Piano Guild Notes, March —April 1969 (Box 300, Folder 3))
  - Piano Guild Notes, Nov. —Dec. 1969 (Box 300, Folder 4))
  - Piano Guild Notes, July —Dec. 1975 (Box 300, Folder 5))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1976 (Box 300, Folder 6))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January-December 1977 (Box 301, Folder 1))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1978 (Box 301, Folder 2))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1979 (Box 301, Folder 3))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January–October 1980 (Box 301, Folder 4))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1981 (Box 301, Folder 5))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1982 (Box 302, Folder 1))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January–December 1983 (Box 302, Folder 2))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January–December 1984 (Box 302, Folder 3))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January–December 1985 (Box 302, Folder 4))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January–December 1986 (Box 302, Folder 5))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1987 (Box 302, Folder 6))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —December 1988 (Box 302, Folder 7))
  - Piano Guild Notes, January —June 1989 (Box 302, Folder 8))
  - Your Musical Cue–School of Music, Indiana University, Nov. 1958; Nov. 1968; March 1969 (Box 303, Folder 1))
  - Your Musical Cue–School of Music, Indiana University, April–Nov. 1969 (Box 303, Folder 2))
  - Your Musical Cue–School of Music, Indiana University, January–April 1970 (Box 303, Folder 3))
  - Your Musical Cue–School of Music, Indiana University, May 1970–January 1971 (Box 303, Folder 4))
  - Your Musical Cue–School of Music, Indiana University, Feb. —Sept. 1971 (Box 303, Folder 5))
  - Your Musical Cue–School of Music, Indiana University, Spring 1973; Winter 1973 (Box 303, Folder 6))
  - Newsletters–Sacred Harp News, March 31, 1971; Sinfonian, Nov. 1958; The Clarion, Feb. 1973; The Tie, Oct. 1971 (Box 303, Folder 7))
  - Aria–Metropolitan Opera National Council, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 303, Folder 8))
  - Opera News, April, May 1999 (Box 303, Folder 9))
  - Youth Music–Music Educators National Conference (Box 303, Folder 10))
  - The Hugo Wolf Society, Volume Six (Box 303, Folder 11))
  - Music for Piano by Robert Pace (Box 303, Folder 12))
  - Tennessee Musicia, Dec. 1972 (Box 303, Folder 13))
  - Indiana University School of Music; New England Conservatory of Music; American Conservatory News–Bulletin; Music at the University of Tennessee; SC/Today (Southern California) (Box 303, Folder 14))
  - Chicago Musical College Quarterly (July 1954); Rudolf Ganz 80th Birthday Celebration (1957); Cincinnati Alumni NewsBulletin, Feb. 18, 1952 (Box 303, Folder 15))
  - Articles on Music–David Amram; Howard F. Brown “Music in the Nashville City Schools” et. al. (Box 304, Folder 1))
  - Handbooks–By-Laws of the National Music Council; Statement of American Guild of Authors and Composers Regarding Revision of U.S. Copyright law; Professional Activities of the Professional Panhellenic Association (Box 304, Folder 2))
  - Campaign for Interlochen Final Report, 2000 (Box 304, Folder 3))
  - Central Tennessee Chapter of the American Guild of Organists Yearbooks, 1950-1954 (Box 304, Folder 4))
  - The Cultural Post (National Endowment for the Arts) June 1975; News from the School of Performing Arts (USC), Sept. —Oct. 1974 (Box 304, Folder 5))
  - Cultural Presentations USA 1967-1968 “A Report to the Congress and the Public by the Advisory Committee on the Arts (Box 304, Folder 6))
  - “An Evaluation of the Performing Arts–The Symphony” (Performing Arts Foundation Kansas City, Missouri) (Box 304, Folder 7))
  - Music News, Nov. 12, 1926–Clarence Gustlin, American Pianist–Lecturer (Box 304, Folder 8))
  - “Music Time with T. Earl Hinton 1968–1969” Middle Tennessee State University (Box 304, Folder 9))
  - Newspaper–The National Student Musician, Oct. 1964, Feb. 5-8 1965, April 1965 (Box 304, Folder 10))
  - Strive–International Music Festivals for Music Educators–Vol. 6, No. 2 (Box 304, Folder 11))
  - “The Tanglewood Symposium–Music in American Society” “The Role of the Cantor” (Box 304, Folder 12))
  - Tennessee 200 Arts and Entertainment Festival–Celebration of the Centuries (Box 304, Folder 13))
  - Handbooks–Woman’s Club of Nashville, Yearbook, 1952- 1953 (Box 304, Folder 14))
  - Yearbook and Musical Directory 1948-49; Memphis and Mid-South Piano Scholarship Assoc.; Tennessee Music Educators Assoc. Membership List, 1947 (Box 304, Folder 15))
  - The Hermitage–Home of General Andrew Jackson, (1930) (Box 305, Folder 1))
  - Booklets–“John Wesley–The Scriptural Christian”; “The Westminster Shorter Catechism”, (1931) (Box 305, Folder 2))